David Thanphilom

2145 Noriega St San Francisco, CA 94122 206-225-4406 <u>davidthanphilom@msn.com</u> <u>http://davidtproductions.com</u>

Summary of Qualifications

Front End Developer with experience in HTML production optimizing Photoshop assets into fully functional responsive websites by coding HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, and jQuery. Has experience building (SPA) single page apps by utilizing MVC frameworks such as AngularJS while making AJAX requests to various API to improve integration of API content. Other experiences include developing custom WordPress themes and working in a fast-paced small team environment communicating effectively to deliver deliverables on time in a rapidly changing environment.

Skills

- HTML5
- CSS3, SASS, LESS
- JavaScript, ES6
- Node JS, NPM, Grunt
- Angular JS, BackboneJS, Handlebars JS
- iQuery
- GIT
- Bootstrap
- WordPress, PHP
- Responsive

Work Experience

Web Developer

Tea Collection Feb 2017 – present

- Worked closely with project Managers, designers, and marketers to update the company website for promotions and new experiences by implementing HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Debug and optimize landing pages improving user experience and site speed.
- Build A/B testing and providing GTM tracking to enhance customer experience by providing marketing with success metrics.
- Worked closely and communicated effectively with backend devs Upshot to role out new features and improvements.

Web Developer

(AppleOne) SamTrans June 2016 – Dec 2016

- Manages CMS daily operation and technical function of website, ensures uptime and resolves any hosting-related issues by serving as the first point of contact.
- Manage and coordinate the integration of Web Service projects (i.e. GTFS static/real-time) between the District and the MTC/511 Transit Data Manager system.
- Built web pages from visual comps by coding HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

Web Developer

(Freelance) Franco Finn April 2016 – June 2016

- Built responsive (SPA) website by implementing BackboneJS, HandlebarsJS, jQuery,
- HTML5, and CSS3.
- Utilized GET AJAX calls to Instagram API to improve website content updateability.
- Implemented Bootstrap and Font Awesome for responsive UI and styles of elements.

Web Developer

(Aquent) Cost Plus World Market March 2015 – Nov 2015

- Implemented HTML, CSS, and JavaScript updates to Cost Plus World Market's website, blog, and corporate site improving usability.
- Edited CPWM WordPress blog theme and widgets to improve usability.
- Applied Admin Tools on CMS Marketlive platform constructing page displays improving version control of files.
- Worked closely with designers, marketing, and project managers to meet project deadlines.

Transferable Skills

- Coordinates many tasks simultaneously
- Excellent communicator with problem solving skills
- Able to prioritize and work proactively
- Self-motivated, hardworking team player

Education

Web Development Certification – 2014 Seattle Central College